When the system breaks down... someone is about to get rich.
Chaos is a drama, action, crime film directed by Tony Giglio.
In Seattle, detective Quentin Conners is unfairly suspended and his partner Jason York leaves the police
force after a tragic shooting on Pearl Street Bridge, when the hostage and the criminal die.
During a bank heist with a hostage situation, Conners is assigned in charge
of the operation with the rookie Shane Dekker as his partner.
The thieves, lead by Lorenz, apparently do not steal a penny from the bank.
While chasing the gangsters, the police team disclose that they planted a virus in the system, stealing
one billion dollars from the different accounts, using the principle of the Chaos Theory.
Further, they find that Lorenz is killing his accomplices.
Det. Quentin Conners, played by Jason Statham.
Det. Shane Dekker, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Lorenz / Jason York, played by Wesley Snipes.
Capt. Martin Jenkins, played by Henry Czerny.
Det. Teddy Galloway, played by Justine Waddell.
Det. Vincent Durano, played by Nicholas Lea.
Chaos is a 2005 American horror film written and directed
by David DeFalco and starring Kevin Gage.
A film about the rape and murder of two adolescent girls, it is an unofficial remake of Wes Craven's
The Last House on the Left, with all character names changed and a different ending.
It The film received negative reviews, in particular
for its use of gore and the ending.
The film explores themes of police, fight, chaos
theory, investigation, power outage.
The tone is emotional.